[{"id":216,"question":"Which is the right syntax for the DISTINCT SQL statement?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT DIFFERENT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_b":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 WHERE table;","answer_c":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":385,"question":"To use 'mysqldbcopy' which privileges are required on the source server?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CREATE","answer_b":"UPDATE","answer_c":"SELECT","answer_d":"INSERT","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":428,"question":"Which level of Abstraction describes what data are stored in the Database?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Physical Level","answer_b":"Logical Level","answer_c":"Abstraction Level","answer_d":"View Level","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"true","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":404,"question":"Which of the following is NOT available in MySQL:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"REVOKE","answer_b":"JOIN","answer_c":"LIKE","answer_d":"FETCH","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":379,"question":"What will be the output of the query SELECT * FROM `members` LIMIT 1, 2;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"the query will generate an error","answer_b":"the query will return all records from the members table","answer_c":"the query will return the first 2 records","answer_d":"the query will return skip the first record then return the following 2 records only","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":437,"question":"What is called if a value shouldn't be greater than 100?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Integrity constraint","answer_b":"Feasible constraint","answer_c":"Over-defined constraint","answer_d":"Referential constraint","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":441,"question":"A table that displays data redundancies yields ________ anomalies","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Insertion","answer_b":"All of options","answer_c":"Update","answer_d":"Deletion","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":430,"question":"Data Warehouse provides","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Transaction Responsiveness","answer_b":"Demand and Supply Responsiveness","answer_c":"Storage, Functionality Responsiveness to queries","answer_d":"None of these","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":390,"question":"MySQL supports different Character Sets, which command is used to display all of them?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SHOW;  ;","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"CHARACTER SET;","answer_d":"SHOW CHARACTER SET","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":418,"question":"MySQL comes with a standard client libraries for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"C Only","answer_b":"PHP And C","answer_c":"Perl,  Java And C","answer_d":"Java Only","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":331,"question":"What is the best advantage of InnoDB over MyISAM?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"InnoDB is thread safe","answer_b":"InnoDB provides a transaction safe environment","answer_c":"InnoDB can handle table with more than 1000 columns","answer_d":"InnoDB provides FULLTEXT indexes","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":"All of the above"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":412,"question":"Which command is used to remove all rows from a table?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Delete","answer_b":"Both Delete and Remove","answer_c":"Truncate","answer_d":"Remove","answer_e":"Drop","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":386,"question":"The Function 'fetchrow_hashref()' returns reference to hash row values keyed by ______________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Row Name","answer_b":"Database Name","answer_c":"Table Name","answer_d":"Column Name","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"},{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":209,"question":"UPDATE keyword is used for:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"to create database elements","answer_b":"to change data","answer_c":"to manage users","answer_d":"to select data","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":250,"question":"Which type you will select if you need to store binary data?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"BLOB","answer_b":"BIGINT","answer_c":"INT","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":"Both BIGINT and INT","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":356,"question":"The WHERE clause is mandatory when using the SELECT command","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":330,"question":"Which is not a  valid bit operator?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"&","answer_b":"&&","answer_c":"<<","answer_d":"|","answer_e":">>","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":400,"question":"One of the early proponents of a Relational Database who laid down many of the principles we use to this day was:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Xigang Koi","answer_b":"Mahatma Coate","answer_c":"William Crawford","answer_d":"Edgar Codd","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":359,"question":"What will be the output of the following query. SELECT * FROM `sales` WHERE amount > 200.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"the query will display all the sales records with amounts starting from 200 and above","answer_b":"the query will output sales records with the amount equal to 200.","answer_c":"the query will display all the sales records with amounts less than 200","answer_d":"the query will display all the sales records with amounts greater than 200","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":363,"question":"What improvements can be made to the query UPDATE students SET `contact number` = 0999;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The query does not need any improvements","answer_b":"enclose the contact number in single quotes","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"}]